ozeki.hu 2019-08-11

# SMS Gateway - Company, Privacy

Ozeki wants to build trust and confidence by promoting fair information practices and ensuring that its visitors retain their privacy when they provide us with personal information or purchase our products. Ozeki reserves the right to update the Privacy Statement at any time without notice to you. The most current version of the Privacy Statement can be reviewed by clicking on the "Privacy Statement" hypertext link located at the bottom of our Web pages. 

Use of Your Personal Information

The personal information we collect from you will be used by Ozeki and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates to provide the service or carry out the transaction you have requested or authorized. This may include using the personal information for the following purposes: 

* To provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications; 
* To make a site or service easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the site or service to your particular interests or preferences; 
* To improve the product or service and to provide better customer service to users. 

Ozeki does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Ozeki may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as packaging, sending and delivering purchases and other mailings, answering customer questions about products or services, processing event registration, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

Ozeki may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Ozeki or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Ozeki and its family of Web sites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Ozeki, its Web sites, or the public. 

Personally identifiable information collected by Ozeki may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Ozeki or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. 

Controlling and Accessing Your Personal Information

Ozeki believes that you should be able to exercise control over how the personal information you provide will be used. If you provide personal information to Ozeki for one purpose, you will be able to opt-out of that personal information being used for other unrelated purposes. 

Please be aware that the choices you make in one context will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to Ozeki in the context of other, separately operated, Ozeki products, sites or services. 

Security of Your Personal Information

Ozeki carefully protects the security of the personal information you provide. Personal information we collect is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access, and we protect this information from loss or misuse, and from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. When sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted over the Internet, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

Use of Cookies On Ozeki Sites

Many Ozeki web sites use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you or your computer, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize a Ozeki web page, or register with a Ozeki site or service, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Ozeki web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized. While some cookies contain personal information, others allow you to customize a site while remaining anonymous. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the sites or services you visit. 

Contact Information 

At Ozeki, we are working hard to protect your privacy, while delivering products that bring you the speed, power and convenience you desire in your personal computing. Our privacy principles represent our commitment to ensuring that your personal information is safe and secure. If you believe that Ozeki has not adhered to these policies, please contact us by e-mail and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
